dayoftheshirt.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy | Day of the Shirt

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

## The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Day of the Shirt website and the Day of the Shirt applications and services for iOS, Android and other devices and platforms, hereafter referred to as simply Day of the Shirt.

Day of the Shirt collects information through user consent. This information includes:

  * Your first name
  * Your chosen username
  * Your email address
  * Your chosen password. A hash of your password is stored in the Day of the Shirt database, and the plain-text password is only used for hash comparison to the stored value.
  * Messages and communications you share with us through email, chat or support tools.

Day of the Shirt collects information through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. This information is collected for the purpose of improving product design, compatibility and customer support, and to identify visitors for the purpose of preventing abuse. This information includes:

  * Your IP address
  * The general geographic location of your IP address and Internet Service Provider
  * Information provided by and about your Internet Browser and Device

We may also use “cookie” technology on our website. Among other things, we may use cookies or other tracking technology for the purposes of tracking your activities on our website. Also, when you click through to visit a merchant, we may redirect you through services that place cookies for sales or affiliate tracking purposes.

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide to operate Day of the Shirt’s features and functionality. We use technologies, such as cookies, to customise content and advertising, to provide social media features and to analyze traffic to the site.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design Day of the Shirt, to suggest popular content to users, and to share with advertisers and publishers. For example:

  * We may change the layout of our website or application based on the number of people that perform a particular action.
  * We may tell an advertiser or publisher that X number of people visited a certain area in our website or application.
  * We may tell an advertiser or publisher that X number of people clicked through a link in our website or application.

When information is used in this or a similar manner, we do not disclose anything that could be used to identify the individuals on whom the information is based.

We may track activities linked to individual accounts to better design Day of the Shirt and suggest relevant content. We also share information about your use of our site with our trusted social media, advertising and analytics partners.

We may disclose your information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or to defend against legal claims. We may disclose your information when we believe it necessary or desirable in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our policies, and/or to protect our rights and property.

In the future, we may sell to, buy, or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets.

## External Services

External services beyond Day of the Shirt’s control are integrated with Day of the Shirt where necessary, such as Intercom for communications, Hotjar for usability research, and Google Analytics for traffic measurement and tracking.

Day of the Shirt makes reasonable efforts to ensure that all integrated external services are trustworthy and reputable, but Day of the Shirt cannot be held responsible for data collection and usage by such services.

## European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

Day of the Shirt strives to be compliant for European Union visitors and users.

  * **Data Protection Officer (DPO)** : Ben Sheldon <dpo@dayoftheshirt.com>
  * **Access and updates to personal data:** Users who have consented to provide personal information can access and update their information through their account on our website.
  * **Deletion of unused personal data** : Day of the Shirt strives the minimize the collection of unused personal data. Unused information not enumerated above will be removed within 1 year.
  * **Request to delete and stop processing data** : Email hello@dayoftheshirt.com
  * **Request to export data** : Email hello@dayoftheshirt.com

## Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email [hello@dayoftheshirt.com](mailto:hello@dayoftheshirt.com). At this time, we only have the ability to receive and send English-language communications.

## Changes To This Policy

Day of the Shirt reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of Day of the Shirt following the posting of changes to this policy will mean you accept those changes.
